Tweek.Privacy policy

Aug 13, 2020

SIA Scada, a private limited company, commercial register number 40103161339, having itsprincipal place of business at European Union, Gustava Zemgala gatve 76, Riga, Latvia ("SIAScada", "us", "we" or "our") operates the www.tweek.so website (the "Service").

We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to thecollection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in thisPrivacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms andConditions, accessible from www.tweek.so

Definitions

Personal Data

Personal Data means data about a living individual who can be identified from those data (or fromthose and other information either in our possession or likely to come into our possession).

Usage Data

Usage Data is data collected automatically either generated by the use of the Service or from theService infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit).

Cookies

Cookies are small pieces of data stored on a User’s device.

Data Controller

Data Controller means a person who (either alone or jointly or in common with other persons)determines the purposes for which and the manner in which any personal data are, or are to be,processed.

For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, we are a Data Controller of your data.

Data Processor (or Service Providers)

Data Processor (or Service Provider) means any person (other than an employee of the DataController) who processes the data on behalf of the Data Controller.

We may use the services of various Service Providers in order to process your data moreeffectively.

Data Subject

Data Subject is any living individual who is the subject of Personal Data.

User

The User is the individual using our Service. The User corresponds to the Data Subject, who is thesubject of Personal Data.

Information Collection And Use

We collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve ourService to you.

Types of Data Collected

Personal Data

While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiableinformation that can be used to contact or identify you ("Personal Data"). Personally identifiableinformation may include, but is not limited to:

● Email address

● First name and last name

● Company name

● Address, State, Province, ZIP/Postal code, City

Cookies and Usage Data

We may use your Personal Data to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotionalmaterials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, orall, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided inany email we send or by contacting us.

Usage Data

We may also collect information how the Service is accessed and used ("Usage Data"). ThisUsage Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol address (e.g. IPaddress), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and dateof your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.

Tracking Cookies Data

We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and holdcertain information.

Cookies are files with a small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier.Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologiesalso used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve andanalyze our Service.

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent.However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.Examples of Cookies we use:

● Session Cookies. We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.

● Preference Cookies. We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences andvarious settings.

● Security Cookies. We use Security Cookies for security purposes.

Use of Data

SIA Scada uses the collected data for various purposes:

● To provide and maintain our Service

● To notify you about changes to our Service

● To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do so

● To provide customer support

● To gather analysis or valuable information so that we can improve our Service

● To monitor the usage of our Service

● To detect, prevent and address technical issues

● To provide you with news, special offers and general information about other goods,services and events which we offer that are similar to those that you have alreadypurchased or enquired about unless you have opted not to receive such information

Retention of Data

SIA Scada will retain your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set outin this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your Personal Data to the extent necessary to complywith our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply withapplicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies.

SIA Scada will also retain Usage Data for internal analysis purposes. Usage Data is generallyretained for a shorter period of time, except when this data is used to strengthen the security or toimprove the functionality of our Service, or we are legally obligated to retain this data for longertime periods.

Transfer Of Data

Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on —computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdictionwhere the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.

If you are located outside Latvia and choose to provide information to us, please note that wetransfer the data, including Personal Data, to Latvia and process it there.

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information representsyour agreement to that transfer.

SIA Scada will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securelyand in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place toan organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security ofyour data and other personal information.

Disclosure Of Data

Disclosure for Law Enforcement

Under certain circumstances, SIA Scada may be required to disclose your Personal Data ifrequired to do so by law or in response to valid requests by public authorities (e.g. a court or agovernment agency).

Legal Requirements

We may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

● To comply with a legal obligation

● To protect and defend the rights or property of SIA Scada

● To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service

● To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public

● To protect against legal liability

Security Of Data

The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over theInternet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commerciallyacceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

"Do Not Track" Signals

We do not support Do Not Track ("DNT"). Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your webbrowser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked.

You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings page of your webbrowser.

Your Rights

We aim to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of yourPersonal Data.

Whenever made possible, you can update your Personal Data directly within your account settingssection. If you are unable to change your Personal Data, please contact us to make the requiredchanges.

If you wish to be informed what Personal Data we hold about you and if you want it to be removedfrom our systems, please contact us.

In certain circumstances, you have the right:

● To access and receive a copy of the Personal Data we hold about you

● To rectify any Personal Data held about you that is inaccurate

● To request the deletion of Personal Data held about you

● You have the right to data portability for the information you provide to SIA Scada. You canrequest to obtain a copy of your Personal Data in a commonly used electronic format sothat you can manage and move it.

Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests.

Service Providers

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service ("ServiceProviders"), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assistus in analyzing how our Service is used.

These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalfand are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose. Including but not limited to:

Analytics

We may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service

Google Analytics

Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports websitetraffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data isshared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize andpersonalize the ads of its own advertising network.

You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service available to Google Analytics byinstalling the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google AnalyticsJavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics aboutvisits activity.

For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy Termsweb page: http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/

Behavioral Remarketing

SIA Scada uses remarketing services to advertise on third party websites to you after you visitedour Service. We and our third-party vendors use cookies to inform, optimize and serve ads basedon your past visits to our Service.

Google AdWords

Google AdWords remarketing service is provided by Google Inc.

You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize the Google DisplayNetwork ads by visiting the Google Ads Settings page: http://www.google.com/settings/adsGoogle also recommends installing the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on -https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout \- for your web browser. Google Analytics Opt-outBrowser Add-on provides visitors with the ability to prevent their data from being collected andused by Google Analytics.

For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy Termsweb page: http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy

Facebook

Facebook remarketing service is provided by Facebook Inc.

You can learn more about interest-based advertising from Facebook by visiting this page:https://www.facebook.com/help/164968693837950

To opt-out from Facebook's interest-based ads follow these instructions from Facebook:https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217

Facebook adheres to the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising establishedby the Digital Advertising Alliance. You can also opt-out from Facebook and other participatingcompanies through the Digital Advertising Alliance in the USA http://www.aboutads.info/choices /,the Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada in Canada http://youradchoices.ca or the EuropeanInteractive Digital Advertising Alliance in Europe http://www.youronlinechoices.eu , or opt-out usingyour mobile device settings.

For more information on the privacy practices of Facebook, please visit Facebook's Data Policy:https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation

Payments

We may provide paid products and/or services within the Service. In that case, we use third-partyservices for payment processing (e.g. payment processors).

We will not store or collect your payment card details. That information is provided directly to ourthird-party payment processors whose use of your personal information is governed by theirPrivacy Policy. These payment processors adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managedby the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, Mastercard,American Express and Discover. PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling ofpayment information.

The payment processors we work with are:

PayPal or Braintree

Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at https://www.paypal.com/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full

Links To Other Sites and Services

Our Service may contain links to other sites and services that are not operated by us. If you clickon a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to reviewthe Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practicesof any third party sites or services.

Children's Privacy

Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 13 ("Children").

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13.

If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us withPersonal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data fromchildren without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from ourservers.

Changes To This Privacy Policy

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by postingthe new Privacy Policy on this page.

We will timely let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, if such revised ornew policy includes a significant change.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this PrivacyPolicy are effective when they are posted on this page.

Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us by email hello@tweek.so
